A Finding Aid to the Ivan C. Karp Papers and OK Harris Works of Art Gallery Records, 1960-2014, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Artist Files, 1967-2014; Series 4; Archival Resource Key; 34 Linear feet Boxes 4-38, 80
  - Current, Photographers, 1983-2103; 4.3; Archival Resource Key
    - O'Kain, Dennis, 1993-2007; Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Onyshko, Wayne, 2001-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - O'Hare, Patrick, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Perrott, Mark, 1983-2012; Archival Resource Key; Includes 5 electronic discs (CD) (Box 25, Folder 11-13)
    - Powell, Luke, 1987-2003; Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Pratt, Greta, 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Putnam, Michael, 2002-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Ranard, John, 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Raney, Susan, 2003-2008; Archival Resource Key; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Rosenheim, Jeff L., 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Rubin, Jeffrey, 1990-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 20-22)
    - Rupp, Sheron, 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - St. Michael, Jonas, 2013; Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Salvo, Dana, 1990-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Scruton, Fred, 2003-2013; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 26-27)
    - Seccombe, David, 2006; Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Sherer, Stan, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Shoots, Jay W., 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Siegel, Steven, 2000-2013; Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 25, Folder 31-32)
    - Sigman, Fred, 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - Sills, Vaughn, 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - Staller, Eric, 1979-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 1-3)
    - Stockdale, John, 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Stravitz, David, 2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Sumida, Kazuo, 2005; Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Stummer, Helen M., 1995-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Suttle, William, 1995-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Teemer, Jack D., Jr., 1990-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Thompson, Thom, circa 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Tilton, Miles, 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Tobia, Blaise, 2013; Archival Resource Key; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Touster, Joshua, 2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Tynan, Jim, 1995-2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Villen, Debra, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Ward, Frank, 1994-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Webber, Nancy, 1978-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 17-20)
    - Welch, Christine, 1996-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Wexler, Mark F., 1993-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Wise, Mark F., 1993-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Wolke, Jay, 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Yglesias, Tom, 2004-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Zamperdi, Luca, 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Zipkin, Harvey, 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Past, Group A, 1970-1979; 4.4; Archival Resource Key
    - Bollinger, Bill, 1972-1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 28-33)
    - Cottingham, Robert, 1971-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 1-7)
    - Woodburn, Stephen, 1971-1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 11-12)
    - Mikus, Eleanor, 1970-circa1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 8-10)
  - Past, Group B, 1967-2014; 4.5; Archival Resource Key
    - Adams, Allan, 1977-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 13-15)
    - Akutsu, Shoichi, 2014; Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Albrecht, Elke, 2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Algardi, Alessandro, 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 18-19)
    - Amar, Joseph, 1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Anastasi, William, 1967-1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Arman, 1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Arndt, Tom, 1973-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Attie, Dotty, 1970s; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Bakaty, Mike, 1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Baladi, Roland, 1980-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 1-3)
    - Baur, Mike, 2008-2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Beardman, John, 1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Beck, Michael, 2012; Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Beltzig, Stefan, 2013; Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Berger, Richard, circa 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Berhang, Mattie, 1982-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 9-12)
    - Bermowitz, Alan, 1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Bianchi, Ben, 1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Bond, Douglas T., 1978-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 15-16)
    - Bower, Gary, 1969-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 17-18)
    - Bowles, Rowell, 2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Bramblett, Frank, 1979-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Brandenburg, Allen, 1982-circa 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Brodsky, Eugene, 1991-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Brown, Larry K., 1979-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 23-24)
    - Buehner, Fritz, 1979-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Butterfield, Deborah, 1976-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 26-29)
    - Calder, Daniel, 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Capps, Kenneth, 1974-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 2-3)
    - Chang, Kuan, 1999-2006; Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Channing, Walter, 1970s; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Chao, Bruce, 1978-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 6-7)
    - Cibula, Ellen, circa 1970s; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Clark, Stephen, 2004-2012; Archival Resource Key; Includes 3 electronic discs (CD) (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Clarke, John Clem, 1969-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 10-13)
    - Corsano, Steven, 2010-2014; Archival Resource Key; Includes 4 electronic discs (CD) (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Creecy, Herbert, 1972-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Cuervas, Joseph, 1989-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Daglish, Jamie, 1991-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Dallas, Ben, 2013; Archival Resource Key; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Davidson, Dan, 1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Davies, John, 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - DeAndrea, John, 1972-2000; Archival Resource Key; Oversized material housed in Box 80 (Box 29, Folder 21-24)
    - Del Rosario, Mariano, 1991-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - Delvecchio, Darryl, 1996-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Dickerson, Brian, 2011-2013; Archival Resource Key; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - DiDonna, Porfirio, 1973-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - D'Orazio, Jon, 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - Douke, Daniel, 1999-2011; Archival Resource Key; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - Edwards, Benjamin, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Elouza, Ramon, 1979-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 2-6)
    - Elsbach, Bart, 2000-2009; Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Erdmann, Allan, 1969-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Erkiletlian, Romaine, 1999-2013; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Erró, 1975-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Evans, Laura, 2009-2012; Archival Resource Key; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Evans, Bruce, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Everett, Bruce, 1970s-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Farber, Manny, 1971-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Forma, Donna, 2012; Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Gallego, Christopher, 2012; Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Galles, Arie, 1972-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Gardner, Frank, circa 1983-circa 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Geyer, John Tully, 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Ghitti, Franca, 2000-2011; Archival Resource Key; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 30, Folder 20-22)
    - Gitlin, Michael, 1975-1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 23-24)
    - Goings, Drew, 2005-2012; Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - Gold, Sharon, 1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - Goldstein, Jack, circa 1969-circa 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 27-28)
    - Gutkin, Peter, 1976-1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Hacklin, Allan, 2011; Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Hammerbeck, Wanda, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Harper, Robert March, 1998-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Herbert, Tom, 1983-2012; Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Herman, Alan, 1978-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 6-7)
    - Hoffman, Martin, 1973-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 8-10)
    - Horn, Gerald, 1978-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Hoskins, Moses, 2006-2013; Archival Resource Key; Includes 3 electronic discs (CD) (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Hrycun, George, 1980s-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Jensz, David, 1993-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 14-15)
    - Jimenez, Luis, 1980s-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Kalloch, Sand T., 2012; Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Kazlov, Brian, 1990-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Kelsey, Steve, circa 1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Kerlin, Sherry, 1980-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Kern, Sandrine, 2013; Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - King, Tony, 2012; Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 USB flashdrive (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Kirkiles, Peter, 2013; Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - Kogge, Robert, 1996-2006; Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Kosianski, Leonard, 2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Kraus, Pavel, 2005-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - Kreznar, Richard J., 1972-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 27-28)
    - Kronquist, Burleigh, 2001-2010; Archival Resource Key; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 31, Folder 29)
    - Krugman, Irene, 1978-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - Lane, Stephen, 1993-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 31)
    - Larsen, Ted, 2008-2012; Archival Resource Key; Includes 3 electronic discs (CD) (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Lee, Unju, 2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Leigh, Harvey, 1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Lesson, Tom, circa 1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Levine, Marilyn, circa 1980s-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Locks, Norman, 1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Lutzke, Richard, 1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Mabe, Joni, 1984-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - MacAdam, Jonathan, 2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - MacCormick, Neil, 2004-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - MacKiewicz, John, 1991-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Mangan, Patrick, 1991-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Mattera, Joanne, 2006-2013; Archival Resource Key; Includes 4 electronic discs (CD) (Box 32, Folder 13-15)
    - Mayer, Edward, 1977-circa 1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 32, Folder 16-17)
    - Mayertchak, Zdeno, 1990-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Meyer, John, 2008-2011; Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Mikus, Eleanore, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Mellon, Joan, 2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Meret, Sasha, 2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Ming, Ju, 1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Minichino, Gina, 2013; Archival Resource Key; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Mito, Mary Neumuth - General, 1981-2005; Archival Resource Key; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - Mito, Mary Neumuth - Photographs, 1977-2005; Archival Resource Key; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Moers, Denny, 1980-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - Monteith, Jerry, 2013; Archival Resource Key (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - Moriarty, Laura, 2012-2014; Archival Resource Key; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - Morley, Malcom, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - Moya, Miguel Angel, 2011; Archival Resource Key; Includes 3 electronic discs (CD) (Box 32, Folder 31)
    - Nagano, Yoko, 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 32, Folder 32)
    - Nakagawa, Naoto, 1972-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 32, Folder 33-34)
    - Nettles, Darryl, 1996-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 32, Folder 35)
    - Noble, Daniel, 1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 32, Folder 36)
    - Okshteyn, Shimon, 1995-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 32, Folder 37)
    - Olsen, Sven-Erik, circa 2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 32, Folder 38)
    - Ossi, James M., 1981-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 32, Folder 39)
    - Owens, Warren, 1972-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Oz, Avital, 1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Perkel, Gregory, 2013; Archival Resource Key; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Poindexter, Ethel, 2011; Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Posen, Stephen, 1970s; Archival Resource Key (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Potters, Ed, 2012; Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Pratt, Vernon, 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Prythero, Tim, 1990-2013; Archival Resource Key (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Quincoces, Alejandro, 2003-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 33, Folder 9-10)
    - Raab, Gail, 1997-2007; Archival Resource Key; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Radetsky, Jack, 2012-2013; Archival Resource Key; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Ramanaskas, Dalia, 1973-1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 33, Folder 13-14)
    - Richardson, Judy, 2013; Archival Resource Key; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Roth, Cora, 2001-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Roth, Frank, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Rowley, Susan Ferrari, 2007-2012; Archival Resource Key; Includes 4 electronic discs (CD) (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Rubins, Nancy, 1979-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 33, Folder 19-21)
    - Runquist, Tollef, 2012-2013; Archival Resource Key; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Russell, Jeff, 1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 33, Folder 23-24)
    - Sandman, Jo, 1973-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 33, Folder 25-29)
    - Schottenfeld, Daniel, 2013; Archival Resource Key (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Schumaker, Ward, 2011-2013; Archival Resource Key; Includes 3 electronic discs (CD) (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Schwartz, Buky, 1976-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 34, Folder 3-5)
    - Scott, Arden, 1974-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Schemchuk, Michael, 2005-2010; Archival Resource Key; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Shaffer, Mary, 2013; Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Siler, Todd, 1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Sloane, Louise P., 1995-2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Sorce, Anthony, 2009; Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Sorcio, Roger, 1976-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Souza, Al, 1974-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 34, Folder 13-17)
    - Spatz-Rabinowitz, Elaine, 2002-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Spratt, Fred, 1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Stavitsky, Ellen, 1997-2010; Archival Resource Key; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Stella, Frank, 1968-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Sunseri, Don, 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Tallman, John, 2009-2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Taylor, Richard, 2007-2011; Archival Resource Key; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Taylor, Stephen, 2006-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Tescher, James C., 2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - Thiele, Robert, 1977-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - Thomas, John Mikel, 1977-2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - Tisdell, Cliff, 2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 34, Folder 29)
    - Tobin, Steve, circa 2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 34, Folder 30)
    - Tuck, Norman, 1970s; Archival Resource Key (Box 34, Folder 31)
    - Turtz, Marilyn, 2012-2014; Archival Resource Key; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 34, Folder 32)
    - Ulrich, Suzanne, 2000-2010; Archival Resource Key; Includes 5 electronic discs (CD) (Box 34, Folder 33-34)
    - Warhol, Andy, circa 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Warren, Shelley, 1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Watt, Roger, 2014; Archival Resource Key; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Weiner, Leslie, 1980-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Weller, Ted, 1977-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Wiener, Sam, 1978-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 6-7)
    - Wilson, Wallace, 1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Wholley, Jay, 1975-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Wood, Tanya, 2013; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Woodburn, Stephen, 1970-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 11-12)
    - Zapkus, Kes, 2008-2014; Archival Resource Key; Includes 4 electronic discs (CD) (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Oversized Material - Group B, John DeAndrea, from Box 29, Folder 21, 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 80)
  - Past, Group C, 1968-2012; 4.6; Archival Resource Key
    - Ackerson, Bruce, 1982-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Algardi, Alessandro, 1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Alongi, Allan, 1996-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Almela, Ramon, 1992-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Appel, Eric, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Arman, 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Aronson, Marc, 2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Balmuth, L. L., 1995-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Bañuelos, Antonio, 2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Barnes, Curt, 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Beltzig, Stefan, 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Ben-Yahuda, Yahuda, 1968-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 25-26)
    - Berger, Carl Brandt, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - Bergman, Lauren, 2004-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 28)
    - Berthot, Jake, 1970s; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 29)
    - Bianchi, Ben, 1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 30)
    - Bollinger, Bill, 1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 31)
    - Bower, Gary, 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 32)
    - Bowles, Rowell, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 33)
    - Bramblett, Frank, 1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 34)
    - Brandt, Sharon, 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 35)
    - Branson, Ortho D., 2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 36)
    - Brecht, Maja Suzanne, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 37)
    - Bronsteen, Earl, 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 38)
    - Brooks, Bruce W., 1993-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 39)
    - Brown, Ross A., 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 40)
    - Brunetti, Erik, 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 41)
    - Buechner, Thomas S., 1993-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 42)
    - Buehner, Fritz, 1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 43)
    - Bultot, Roger, 1996-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 44)
    - Butcher, Steve, 1995-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 45)
    - Capps, Kenneth, 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 46)
    - Carlisle, Tamara, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 47)
    - Cash, Sidney, 2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 48)
    - Caulfield, Patrick, 1970s; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 49)
    - Chang, Kuan, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 50)
    - Chansky, Matt, 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 51)
    - Chao, Bruce, 1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 52)
    - Chapin, Steve, 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 53)
    - Chiang, Paul, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 54)
    - Chitjian, Tigran, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 55)
    - Cibula, Ellen, 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 56)
    - Clark, Ronald, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 57)
    - Clarke, John Clem, 1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 58)
    - Corrodi, Mark, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 59)
    - Creecy, Herbert, 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 60)
    - Cuevas, Joseph, 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 61)
    - Cuni, Pedro, 2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 62)
    - Davis, John, 2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 63)
    - Davies, Sally, 1995-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 64)
    - Depasquale, James, 1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 65)
    - Deschamps, François, 1991-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 66)
    - DiDonna, Porfirio, 1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 67)
    - Diller, Ben, 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 68)
    - D'Orazio, Jon, 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 69)
    - Durlach, David, 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 70)